# **MAITRI GUPTA**

Ahmedabad, India | maitrigupta08@gmail.com

#### **SECURITY ANALYST**

As an graduate IT student with a specialization in cyber security, I have spent the last year actively involved in this field. With experience as a cyber security researcher, and bug bounty hunter, I have honed my skills in identifying and addressing security vulnerabilities and threats.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Security Analyst | TechDefenders Consulting

Sept 2024 - Present

- Penetration Testing
- Vulnerability Assessment

# Intern Security Analyst | TechDefenders Consulting

Oct 2023 - July 2024

- Linux Essentials
- Vulnerability Assessment
- Reconnaissance

# **SKILLS**

- VAPT
- Creative Problem-Solving
- Photography

- Cyber Security
- Critical Thinking
- Social Media Marketing

#### **EDUCATION**

## Gujarat University | Ahmedabad

Sept 2021 - June 2024

- SGPA: 6.22
- Worked with various technologies including virtualization.

## 12th (Commerce) | NIOS

June 2019 - June 2021

• GPA: 70%

10th (CBSE) | DPS

June 2018 - March 2019

• CGPA: 70%

#### **INTERESTS**

- VollyBall
- Chess
- Music

- Acting
- karate
- Badminton

#### **AWARDS**

- Vollyball State Level (2018)
- District Level Intern Championship Karate (2017)
- Cricket Tournament at Gujarat University (2021)
- Badminton Tournament at Gujarat University (2021)